(Amy:)Read about it in your book.
(Bernadette:)Why would you be embarrassed
to tell us?
I'm not. I didn't want anyone to know.
I haven't told Leonard yet.
- Why wouldn't you tell Leonard?
- Because it's me going back to school.
(Penny:)And he's gonna be all,
"You can do it," and, "How can I help?"
And, "I'm so proud of you." Ugh.
I can't believe you could keep
something like that from him.
(Amy:)You guys have got to be
the weirdest couple I know.
(Penny:)Really?
(Penny:)You can't think of anyone weirder?
(Amy:)I can...
(Amy:)...but she's sitting right there.
Yes. I play the word "quiver"...
(Sheldon:)...with a triple letter
and a double word score for 72 points.
That'll let the air out of your tires,
Hawking.